Do you know how sexy you are / 你知道你有多性感吗
Do you know how wild you make me / 你知道你让我变得多狂野吗
And it's not your body, your car / 不是你的身体或你的车
It's the way you give and take me / 而是你给予和对待我的方式
I was just a lonely soul / 我曾是个寂寞灵魂
Looking for someone / 找寻着一个
to free me from this stormy weather / 能把我从暴风雨中解救出来的人
And now it's always sun and summer together / 现在则常是晴空盛夏
Do you know how dirty you are / 你知道你有多坏吗
From the earth you came to love me / 从尘世而来却爱上我
And you're so much brighter than stars / 你比星星都耀眼很多
But you're here with me and not above me / 但你陪伴着我而不是凌驾于我之上
I was just a lonely boy / 我曾是个寂寞男孩
Looking for someone / 找寻着一个
to free me from this dark forever / 能把我从黑夜里永久解救出来的人
And now it's always sun and summer together / 现在则常是晴空盛夏
Do you know how sexy you are / 你知道你有多性感吗
Do you know how hopeless I am / 你知道我有多无望吗
hope left me when I met you / 遇见你后希望就离我而去
'Cause I don't need to wish or pretend / 因为我不必再许愿或者假装
to find someone to help me get through / 能找到人来帮我度过难关
I was just a lonely boy / 我曾是个寂寞男孩
Looking for someone / 找寻着一个
to free me from this dark forever / 能把我从黑夜里永久解救出来的人
And now it's always sun and summer together / 现在则常是晴空盛夏
Do you know how sexy you are... / 你知道你有多性感吗…
Do you know how sexy you are / 你知道你有多性感吗